That piercing noise...
What is this place?
An amusement park?
I've never been here before.
Why in the world am I riding on
a Ferris wheel in my pajamas?
How'd I get here?
The desert.
I remember being in the desert, riding
through Saudi Arabia on camelback.
But where are the others?
Did they abandon me?
This isn't making any sense.
There's not a soul anywhere
in the amusement park.
So why do I hear the cries of a baby?
And for that matter, where is it?
This card is...
Death 13!
Oh no, the card is moving!
Kaku-ing!
Kaku-ing! Kaku-ing!
Hey, take it easy.
Stop screaming and shaking the bed like
that creepy girl from The Exorcist.
You're weirding me out.
Where are we?
Don't ask stupid questions.
Now come on and get up already, would ya?
After breakfast, we're
gonna take to the skies.
Looks like another scorcher today.
I had a terrible nightmare.
It was truly horrifying.
You don't say.
Lay on the details.
I want to hear all about it.
Well, the thing is, I can't remember.
I've forgotten it all.
Come again?
Regardless, it was petrifying.
But when you woke me up,
you pulled me out of it.
Wish we could talk more about it,
but we've got to get a move on.
Let's go.
Hurry up and get ready.
There's a cut on my hand.
But how'd it get there?
And now I'm going to be a star dust?
A hundred years ago, I'm
called to be a star dust.
The men are going towards the
end of the tunnel of the time.
It's like a karma.
It's a destiny.
Jotaro and Mr.
Joestar are already headed to the
plane, so we'll meet them there.
And the way I hear it, we're
traveling 500 kilometers today.
No!
This can't be happening!
Please stop, my poor dog!
My dog is dead!
Who would do such a thing? A dog?
Dog?
I could have sworn that I saw
a dead dog not too long ago.
Whoever did this is sick, but
there's nothing we can do about it.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hold on a dang second there, mister!
What exactly do you mean you
can't sell us the plane now?
I seem to recall you taking my money
last night and saying it was a done deal.
You'll get a full refund, but first
we need to see to a baby with a fever.
It's 39 degrees Celsius. Huh?
There's no doctor in this town,
so we have no choice but to take
the baby somewhere else to get help.
Okay, then, what do you say to
us taking that plane over there?
I'm sorry to say that one's broken.
What's up?
Some kind of argument?
Yeah.
A baby?
A baby.
I remember hearing a baby's cries.
But where?
You'll be able to use the plane
after it gets back tomorrow night.
We can renegotiate and talk prices then.
Did you say tomorrow night?
Our group has someone's life on
the line just like you guys do.
We can't afford to spend two
days pissing around this place.
So, what you're telling me is
you'd rather let that baby die?
Well, I...
Excuse me, I have a suggestion.
We can kill two birds
with one stone by having
these gentlemen taken to
the doctor on their way.
Nice idea, but...
The Cessna is built to carry four, but
surely there's enough room for a baby.
I could have sworn I just saw it smile.
And that the child already has teeth.
You sure about this, lady?
Do you really want to leave
your baby with these guys?
Uh, just a minute.
We can't do that either.
It's too dangerous for
the baby to come with us.
I told him this would be dangerous.
Hey, just try and take it easy, Mr.
Joestar.
There's no way a stand could catch a plane
flying hundreds of kilometers an hour.
I mean, we even made sure the
plane itself wasn't a stand.
I'd say we're good to go.
I'm far more worried about the old man's
flying than I am in
attack from enemy stands.
Oh, thank goodness.
What a relief.
By the way, I wonder who
that baby belonged to. Huh?
Are you saying you're not the
mother of that child, miss?
Oh, no.
I found it by the well this morning.
Though, from the moment I heard the babies
crying, I wasn't able to help myself.
I felt I had to put him on that plane.
What could happen?
Maybe it's just me, but I always
get so tired when I get on a plane.
If it's all right with you, Mr.
Joestar, I think I'm going
to take a Monday catnap.
Sure!
What is this?
Hey, Kakyoin, where the hell
are we? Where'd Mr. Joestar go?
This is the same dream I had this morning.
But now it seems we're
both inside the dream.
What? A dream? Yes.
That's a relief.
It's just a stupid dream.
I was worried for a second.
But if it's only a dream,
who cares if the dog is dead?
Polnareff, you can't be serious.
Dreams are only as scary as you make them.
That's kind of the way it goes.
Oh, just try and relax.
How can I relax when we're
having the same dream?
I suppose you have a point there.
This is kind of weird.
But in a dream, isn't anything possible?
Oh, boy, would you look at that!
This dreaming thing is great!
So good!
See?
All you have to do to make your
dreams fun is think they're fun.
Listen, do you remember seeing
the dog's carcass this morning?
Obviously, the dog and
I had the same dream,
and in that dream, that dog
was unmistakably slaughtered.
Once I was awake, I found
this cut on my hand.
Where from?
From the enemy's stand. Death 13.
The enemy's stand. Mm-hmm.
Oh, I get it now.
You're paranoid because you
had a dream about stands.
Man, you have got to take it easy.
You're wrong.
It wasn't a dream about stands.
A stand was in my dream.
That's what I said, you were
having a dream about stands.
Ah, you still don't get it, do you?
Loli-ho!
Tell me, does it hurt being that stupid?
Oh, for the love of, let
me spell it out for you.
I'm saying that you're slow
on the uptake, palmer-up.
It's coming from the dog's wound.
Lo-de-ho!
Allow me to welcome
you to my humble abode!
This is a dream, and I'm the Grand Reaper!
It's a megaphone?
What the...
what is that thing?
Polnareff, stay on
guard and watch closely.
That fiend is Death 13!
Come forth, Hierophant Green!
Hierophant, attack!
Giorno!
Why can't I summon Hierophant?
What is this?
I can't get my stand to appear either!
Is it because we're in some
kind of twisted dream? Alley-ho!
It's romantic, wouldn't you agree?
Being able to die in a dream?
Alley-ho!
Jotaro, do you sense that?
Yeah, clear as day.
Are you stupid?
Surely you know by now that
only a stand can defeat a stand.
It's time for you to enter
your eternal sleep, Pone Ref.
Alley-o!
Pull the ref! Die!
Pull the ref.
Hey, Polnareff, wake up!
It would appear our little
traveler has wet himself.
Do us all a favor and change his diaper.
Curses!
Someone must have woken
the fool from his slumber.
He's quite lucky.
Lollyho, I suppose it's no matter.
Even if he wakes up, he won't
remember a single thing.
I'll just have to finish him
the next time he falls asleep.
Which means your death has been moved up.
Lollyho!
Hey there, Polnareff.
Have you woken up yet?
I like that diaper change this year.
All right, I'm up, I'm up.
Man, I feel like I had some
kind of terrifying nightmare.
But I don't remember what happened at all.
I've completely forgotten.
After you change the boy's diaper,
you can head back to dreamland
to finish your business.
I won't wake you up again
Mad hold on a second guys.
What the hell is this the kid
took a dump in his diaper.
Just look at the size of
it Well, he is a baby.
You know, that's why he wears diapers.
You're kidding me.
That's why
Say, Douglas.
What a vile, disgusting creature.
And he's gotten it all over the place.
Would you stop yapping and
change the damn diaper already?
It stinks.
How are you not embarrassed?
Do us all a favor and grow up already.
Does this look right to you?
Well, it looks good to me.
Jotaro, I need you to
hold on to the edge there.
I'm gonna try and pin it.
Okay. Like this?
Yeah, I think so.
Now hold on to the baby.
Stop it!
Kick, what's wrong? Hey!
Damn it!
I've lost control!
Wait, are you saying that
we're going to crash? Stop!
Kakyoin, what's the matter with you?
He's been this way since he woke up!
I don't care, just calm him down!
Old man, if you don't regain control
of this thing, we're all done for!
Kakyoin, you need to pull
yourself together pronto!
We're about to crash because of you!
Lally-ho!
Talk about a restless sleeper.
At this rate, you'll kill us both.
You and my user, that is.
Your user is that baby?
How in the world is that possible?
No way.
He's only about six months old.
Wrong!
I'm 11 months, almost a year old.
It may also interest you
to know that I'm a genius.
I may poop in my diapers, but I know
a hell of a lot more than you fools.
Yaaaaaah!
And with that, you've lost
your ability to scream.
A stand within a dream.
I have to find a way to let Mr.
Joestar and Jotaro know.
Hm?
What are you doing, Mr.
Joespawn?
Damn it, level us out!
Just calm down!
Can't you see I'm working on that while
trying to stay cool and collected?
I'm not waking up!
Lally-ho!
Looks to me like no one's going
to notice if you're cutting
your arm with a knife that's
smaller than my wee-wee!
Besides, you can hurt yourself all you want
in this dream, but it won't wake you up!
As long as you're asleep, I completely
control every iota of your precious mind.
My stand, Death 13,
infiltrates the minds of its slumbering
victims when they are at
their most vulnerable.
Dammit! Stop!
What's wrong, old man?
We're crashing!
I'll control it with Hermit Purple!
I did it!
I lifted the plane just
in the nick of time!
What a close one!
It would seem we managed
to avoid crashing.
That was too close for comfort.
Now then, what do you see to me killing
you by crushing that heart of yours?
That way,
Joestar and the others will think you had
a heart attack and died of natural causes.
Die, Cuckooine!
Did you guys see that?
How do you boys like them apples?
My flying's not too shabby!
What?
Why the hell is there a palm
tree all the way out here?
Good grief. Damn.
I knew you'd do this!
Is this enough, Mr. Joestar?
Yeah, thank you.
We survived, butt.
Kakyoin, what's going on, man?
This is all your fault, you know.
I'm not sure.
I feel like I just
endured a horrible dream.
And when I awoke, I was utterly exhausted.
I think there's something wrong with me.
Try and cheer up.
It's probably a case of fatigue.
It's been about a month
now since we left Japan.
And the enemy's been attacking
us non-stop ever since that day.
Hey.
It looks like the baby's
fever has finally gone down.
Thank goodness he's safe and sound.
If anything were to happen to this
little guy, I'd never forgive myself.
Ah!
Peek-a-boo!
Blah!
He has such an adorable
smile, don't you think?
I really don't get what's so funny.
You're not even making
any jokes, just faces.
What an idiot.
Oh, put a sock in it.
This isn't my idea of
a perfect night either.
Hey, old man, the radio survived.
What should we do?
Should we send out an SOS?
That'll mean Dio can find
us, but... We have to.
Let's call for a rescue,
for the baby's sake.
Huh?
I thought I was feeling
twinches of pain. I'm bleeding.
Wait, did I cut it when we crashed?
What's this?
The cuts form letters.
Baby stand but how did they I don't
know what it means even though it's
my handwriting I can't remember
anything did I do this to myself there
isn't any blood on my knife but it
seems the cuts were made with this blade
wait a minute could I have really
forgotten violently cutting my own arm?
Damn it!
I was told he was clever,
but I never thought he'd actually
carve letters into his arm?
while trying to wake himself up.
What was that look on
the baby's face just now?
It's as if he deliberately looked
away the moment I met his gaze.
Baby.
Baby, stand.
I hate to say it, but I might
be losing my mind, because...
I'm starting to think...
that this baby is a stand user!
Hey, Kakyoin, what do
you think you're doing?
Come on, now.
That is way too rough.
You can strangle the boy.
What's wrong with you?
My apologies.
There, there.
Everything's all right.
Let's have something to eat, shall we?
He should calm down once
he has some food in him.
Hey, Jotaro.
It looks like poor Kakyoin's really
starting to lose it out here.
Hmm. There, there.
I wonder if he'll make it
through the rest of this trip.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick!
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They got their money on
a bed Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tight to the hookah? I say,
walk
like
an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays,
spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids.
So sick of books?
They're like the punk.
And the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking.
Like an Egyptian.
All the kids. In the marketplace.
Walk
like
an Egyptian.
Did you see that?
Knock it off, Cockyween.
That's enough.
How stupid can you be?
But I'm sure that he's a stand user!
You didn't do that to yourself, did you?
What's going on?
Did I make things even worse?
Not at all!